Guide to the Physics Department records, 1930-2005 RG0077
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Faculty records, 1930-1995; Series 9; 3.5 Linear Feet
  - Companions in Zealous Research, 1976; Series 9 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Passport and Maple guides, 1983-1987; Series 9 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Norm overflow, 1983; Series 9 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Three body research, 1983-1994; Series 9 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Angular reducton, 1986; Series 9 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Cartesian coupling, 1988; Series 9 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Three body notes, 1991-1992; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Three body state papers, 1994; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Aerovest, Inc., 1994; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Original folder titled, "W. Parke, Physics Dept. GWU Wash. DC, USA", 1995; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Draft of VI/263 - VI/277, 1995; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - GWU Folders, Undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Use of Current Conservation Laws in Nuclear Beta Decay, Undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Notes, Undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Notes, Undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Notes, Undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Photos "Scientists are people too", Undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - von Karman, Undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Notes from various lectures, Undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 13)